[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Transport is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Fully_Connected is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Hybrid is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Dairy_Chairs is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Satellites is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Microwave is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Negative_Filter is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Single_Homed_Bastion is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Screened_Host_Firewall is a subClass from Packet_Fittering_Routers","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASET is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"CD is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASE5 is a subClass from Gigabit_Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VRP is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Rule_Based_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Anomaly_Detection is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_5 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_2 is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Protocol is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Security is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Performance is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Confidentiality is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Twisted_Ribbon_Cable is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bridge is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Gateway is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network_Interface is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Layer is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Virtual_Private_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Intrusion_Detection_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is a subClass from Firewall","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from ISO_Standard","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Application","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Forwarding is a subClass from Presentation","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Point_to_Point","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Mesh","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is a subClass from Hybrid","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Virus","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Logic_Bomb","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Stealth_Virus is a subClass from Backdoor","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Infrared","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Satellites","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Silicon_Photo_Diode is a subClass from Microwave","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from BOOTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMPv1 is a subClass from NTP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from VOIP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from eMail","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is a subClass from Internet_Society","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Yahoo is a subClass from World_Wide_Web","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Yahoo is a subClass from IAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Yahoo is a subClass from G","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ExtremeXOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from ZyNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extreme_Network is a subClass from VRP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from CISCO_IOS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from JUNOS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cisco_Inc. is a subClass from MOS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from User_Datagram_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from Internet_Protocol_Version_6","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is a subClass from Connectionless_Service","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from SMTP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from DNS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is a subClass from DICT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from IMAP","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from Bit_Torrent","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP2 is a subClass from HTTPS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from SSH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from FTP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SCP is a subClass from SNMP","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Honeypots","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Rule_Based_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Pure_Honeypots is a subClass from Anomaly_Detection","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from ","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from Type_5","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Variable_Bit_Rate is a subClass from Type_2","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from SDH","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from Internet_Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"STS-1 is a subClass from Ethernet","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from Networking_Hardware","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switch is a subClass from Topology","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Performance","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Network_Operating_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Congession is a subClass from Scale","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Local_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Campus_Area_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Home_Area_Network is a subClass from Backbone_Network","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Public_Key_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Hash_and_Mac_Algebra","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Elliptic_Curve_Cryptography is a subClass from Digital_Signature","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from Symmetrie_Encryption","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Block_Cipher is a subClass from Fabrication","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Active_Attacks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Availablity","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Optical_Fibre","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is a subClass from Coaxial_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Shielded_Foiled_Twisted_Pair","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Bonded_TP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is a subClass from Twisted_Ribbon_Cable","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Modem","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Bridge","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Transport_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Network_Interface","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Socket_Address is a subClass from Internet_Layer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Server","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Router_Operating_System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Novel_Netware is a subClass from Peer_to_Peer","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from AAL","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from Data","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Type_1 is a subClass from Video","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":null,"choices":[],"strategy":null},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ATM_Layer is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Switched is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Scope is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Infrared is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Loaded_TP is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Flooders is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model is  Open Systems Interconnection","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Remote Desktop Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Media Gateway Control Protocol (MGCP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Network Management Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Object Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is direct sequence spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TLS is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is  Real Time Streaming Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Voice over Internet Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Gnutella is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Integrity is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bonded_TP is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Honeypots is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Permanent is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Brouter is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Bandwidth is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Intranet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Telnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Internet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Ethernet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BACnet is  Building Automation and Control Networks","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP is Hypertext Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is SSH File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Session Description Protocol (SDP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSH is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NFS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is frequency hopping spread spectrum","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NNTP is Network News Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DTLS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DNS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DOS is denial-of-service attack","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Simple Mail Transfer Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"BASET2 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET4 is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASETX is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"BASET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ARPANET is  Advanced Research Projects Agency Network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DTLS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DOS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DNS is Domain Name System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DICT is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Engineering Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDM is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SDH is Synchronous Optical Networking (SONET) and Synchronous Digital Hierarchy (SDH)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is Lightweight Directory Access Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Internet Assigned Numbers Authority","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"POP1 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PHP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"PPP is  Point to Point Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SDH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is Secure Shell","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP2 is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"POP is Post Office Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PHP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IAX is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Internet Architecture Board","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSTP is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FHSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CSS is  chirp spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMB is Server Message Block","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"PPTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Protocol television","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TDM is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTTP is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HTML is HyperText Markup Language","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"ZyNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"JUNOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Network is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Direct_DS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NetBIOS is  Network Basic Input Output System","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DICT is Dictionary Server Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"QAM is Quadrature amplitude modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"QAM is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CMAC is Cipher-based message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IPTV is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IETF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IRTF is Internet Research Task Force","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Class_B is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Plastics is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Cells is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_F is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_C is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_D is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_Fa is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Star_Mesh is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_E is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Wireless is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Class_A is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RIP is Routing Information Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"VOIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SIP is Session Initiation Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"MPPE is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IDEA is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MIME is Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"TLS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"THSS is Time hopping spread spectrum ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTX is Fiber to the x","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTC is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"TFTP is Trivial File Transfer Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Internet message access protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SNTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SFTP is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"FTTN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"STUN is Session Traversal Utilities for NAT","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ASP is Active Server Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SSTP is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSH is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DSSS is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SSB is single sideband modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IANA is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"LDAP is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"AAL is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"WLAN is wireless local area network","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"HTML is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"DHCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"HMAC is hash message authentication code","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IMAP is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAB is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IANA is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"IAX is Inter-Asterisk eXchange (IAX)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SOAP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"JSP is JavaServer Pages","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NNTP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"MGCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NCP is NetWare Core Protocol","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RDP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTP is Real-time Transport Protocol (RTP)","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"FTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RTSP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"NTP is Network Time Protocol ","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"IP_Suite is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"CISCO_IOS is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"OSI_Model is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SVOIP is Secure Voice over IP","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"SMB is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SMTP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SNMP is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"SM is space modulation","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"property"}]